claro-search.com 2017-08-06

# None

This privacy policy applies to the Toolbar and Search Software and each of the related Web sites (the "Web Sites") maintained by Babylon Ltd. ("we" or "us"). In the event of any inconsistency between this privacy policy and a policy listed on one of the other Web Sites, this policy shall control. We do not collect personal identification information including names, phone numbers and addresses. Users might be asked to add their email address to get information about Babylon Software and other special offers from Babylon Ltd. We do collect information necessary to enable certain features in the Toolbar Platform. We do not sell, rent or trade any personally identifiable information you provide when using the Toolbar, Search Software or the Web Sites. Babylon Ltd. is the entity that collects the information either through the Software or as a result of the Software being installed or used (including through third party software being downloaded through the Toolbar and/or Search Software). Babylon Ltd. is committed to its users’ data security and takes serious steps for the maximum data security. We gather certain information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser user agent, referring page, date/time stamp and cookies and web beacons automatically. We use such information to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information to better provide our services and to facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisement and web searches. When you visit the Babylon Ltd's Web Sites or use the Search Software, we may place a small text file-called a "cookie"-on your computer that allows us to improve the quality of our service, and to store your preferences and settings. Importantly, a cookie does not allow us to obtain any personally identifiable information (such as your real name or address) unless you have specifically provided such information when using the Web Sites or the Software. The search feature sends a request to our servers from time to time including while processing a search query that you have inputted or a third party software download that you have approved This request includes the keyword query, source (Toolbar, IE bar, related links, etc…) and/or third party software offer details you approved and all HTTP data transferred automatically by the browser (IP Address, User Agent, Cookies, web beacons etc…). We use this information in order to properly process your search request, downloads facilitated by the Search Software and to make our Services, offers and advertising communication with you more relevant to your interest. For example, this data provides us with information on which language you prefer to use and your geographical location. Such information is recorded on a non-personally identifiable basis and is kept strictly anonymous. If any of the Web Sites or the Software is ever sold or all or substantially all of the assets relating to a Web Site or the Software are transferred to another entity, we may transfer all information provided by or collected from you, including personally identifiable information, in order to ensure continuity of your service. We will disclose information, including personally identifiable information, data acquired by cookies, and other data, where required by a subpoena, interception order or other lawful process. We also reserve the right to disclose such information when we believe, in our sole judgment and to the extent consistent with applicable law, that such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights or safety of others or to enforce, or protect our rights under, this Agreement.
